

## **SHARLENE BLAS**

A self-motivated IT professional with a solid experience in web development and proficiency in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, Vue.js framework and responsive web development, as well as strong skills and ability in writing clean and efficient code, seeks the position of Front-End Developer.

#### **EDUCATION**

# AMA COMPUTER LEARNING CENTER

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

### **SKILLS**

HTML Windows deployment server

CSS C#

JQuery MySQL

Javascript Restful WebServices

Vue.js Postman

Nuxt.js Vsts

Typescript Shopify

Bootstrap Wordpress

Vuetify Stripe payment

Quasar Vessel Bulma Git UI Kit Alipay

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Nov. 2020 to Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Yondu.Inc

Feb. 2020 to Nov. 2020

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

BigdishPlc

June 2018 to October 2019

**FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER** 

Infotouch System Inc

### **PROJECTS**

Bangko Sentral ng Pilipinas (BSP) Technology used: Vue.js 2, Vuetify

Maynilad

Technology used: Vue.js 3, Composition API, Quasar

S&R door Card Scanner and Admin Panel

Technology used: Vue.js, Quasar

Yondu Website

Technology used: Wordpress

Pitmasters Glife app & website

Technology used: Nuxt.js, Vue.js, Miniapp, Alipay

Bench Glife app

Technology used: Miniapp, Alipay

Vivo Glife app

Technology used: Miniapp, Alipay

Restaurant delivery system

Technology used: Nuxt.js, Vue.js Bootstrap, Stripe

payment

TRAINING HUNTING WEBSITE

Technology used: Bootstrap, Vue.js, c#, MySQL

#### **CONTACTS**

■ blas.sharlene@gmail.com

**Q** 0936-444-2394

Valenzuela City